I build ad slots in my app because I hate ads.
我在自己的 App 里做广告位，因为我讨厌广告。
Yup, I know how that sounds, so let me explain.
是的，我知道这话听着像什么，所以让我解释一下。
I could've made DirtBikeX full of flyers and banners, and honestly, that'd be the easy way out.
我本可以把 DirtBikeX 做得满是传单和横幅广告，说实话，那才是最省事的做法。
But I hate ads so much that I literally look away or close my eyes so that they don't get into my head
但我太讨厌广告了，以至于我真的会把目光移开或者闭上眼睛，不让它们进到我脑子里
And I definitely want no riders opening my app and feel like they walked into a damn billboard.
而且我绝对不希望有骑手打开我的 App，感觉像是走进了一块该死的广告牌。
So these slots work differently. There are limited passes for real riders who actually belong in the sport.
所以这些广告位的运作方式不一样。有数量有限的通行证，留给真正属于这项运动的真实骑手。
Here, you can go to the Sponsorship page and pick your spots.
在这里，你可以进入赞助页面，挑选你的位置。
Choose when it starts, choose how long it runs, and DirtBikeX got you covered.
选择开始时间，选择投放时长，剩下的 DirtBikeX 都帮你搞定。
Then, your profile will show up in multiple places across the app where people are actively looking
然后，你的个人主页会出现在 App 里的多个位置，正好是大家在主动寻找的地方
And the biggest one is the splash screen, where users can pause it, tap your face, and go straight into your profile.
其中最大的一个是启动页，用户可以把它暂停，点一下你的脸，直接进入你的个人主页。
And don't worry, to keep it fair, passes are capped and rotated, so nobody gets to flood the scene.
别担心，为了保证公平，通行证有数量上限并且会轮换，所以没人能淹没整个圈子。
And you even get to check your sponsorship stats too.
而且你还能查看自己的赞助数据。
Regional exposure, daily trends, you name it.
区域曝光、每日趋势，应有尽有。
So essentially, it's a fair way to get seen by the right people.
所以本质上，这是一种公平的方式，让对的人看见你。
My name is Rubio, and I'm giving out day passes for free.
我叫鲁比奥，我在免费送出单日通行证。
Comment "PASS", and I'll see you in the app.
评论 “PASS”，我们 App 里见。